A Guide to the David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, RG 49 FA1506
Rockefeller Archive Center
- David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, 49; 27.14 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 record storage box.
  - Conservation, 1997-2000; 8; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Conservation - G-P, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Historic Massachusetts, Long Island Pine Barrens Society, Monterey Bay Aquarium, National Park Foundation, National Trust for Historic Preservation, Natural Resources Council of Maine, Natural Resources Defense Council, Northern Forest Center, Ocean Conservancy (in memory of John A. Anderson), Park Partners Initiative.
    - Conservation - Q-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Rainforest Alliance, ReSource Institute for Low Entropy Systems, Spindletop, Student Conservation Association, Inc., Sustainable Development Institute, Texas Wild Fort Worth Zoo, Trust for Public Land, Trustees of Reservations, Wildlife Conservation Society, World Wildlife Fund, Yellowstone Park Foundation, Yosemite National Institutes Educational Adventures in Nature's Classroom.
    - Alaska Fund for the Future, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The Conservation Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - National Audubon Society, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Audubon Bird-a-thon
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - National Fish-Wildlife Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Nature Conservancy, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Foreign - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Foreign - Conservation International, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous States - A-Z (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous States - Nature Conservancy - Maine Chapter, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - New York City - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      The African Council, Trees New York, Wave Hill.
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Heather Garden (Fort Tryon Park), 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - New York State - A-L, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Dutchess Land Conservancy, Friends of Rockefeller State Park Preserve, Hudson Riverkeeper
    - New York State - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      New York Parks and Conservation Association, New York State Office of Parks, Recreation and Historic Preservation. Palisades Interstate Park Commission, Riverkeeper, Rockefeller State Park Preserve, Scenic Hudson, Teatown Lake Reservation, Westchester Land Trust, Wildlife Rescue and Rehabilitation Network of Westchester County, Inc.,
    - New York State - Columbia Land Conservancy, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Acadia National Park (Friends of Acadia), Mesa Verde National Park, Old Faithful Visitor Center, Yellowstone National Park, Yosemite National Institute.
    - Recreation - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Randall's Island Sports Foundation
    - Recreation - Chess-in-the-Schools, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - D-E, 1997-2000; 9; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Defense - Veterans - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Navy League of the United States. World Security Organization.
  - Economics, 1997-2000; 10; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Economics - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bretton Woods Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Citizens for a Sound Economy Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Economic Policy Review, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Institute for International Economics, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Trilateral Commission, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 4, Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Education, 1997-2000; 11; 4.56 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes
    - Education - A-M, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2-5)
    - Education - N-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - American Academy of Achievement, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Children's Storefront, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Public Administration, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - A-K, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
    - Colleges - L-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - American Academy in Berlin, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - American University in Cairo, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Bard College - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Bard College Performing Arts Center, Center for Curatorial Studies.
    - Colleges - Brandeis University, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Brown University, Providence, R.I., 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - Cambridge College, Cambridge, Massachusetts (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Baruch College, City College, Graduate Center Foundation, Inc., Lehman College.
    - Colleges - College Fund-United Negro College Fund (UNCF), 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - College of the Atlantic, Bar Harbor, Maine, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - American Assembly, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Knight-Bagehot Fellowship Program, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - School of International and Public Affairs, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Proposal to establish the David Rockefeller School
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller Center at Darmouth College
    - Colleges - Emory University - The Carter Center, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Colleges - Georgetown University, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - London School of Economics and Political Science - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - London School of Economics - Dinner, 1998 November 11 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Art Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Asia Center, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard College Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Contributions, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John King Fairbank Center for East Asian Research, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Fundraising, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Management Company, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 25, Folder 11, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Memorial Church, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Phillips Brooks House Association, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - President and Fellows of Harvard University, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Michael C. Rockefeller Memorial Fellowship, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Signet Society, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Weapons of Mass Destruction, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Polytechnic University, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Pratt Institute, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Spelman College, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - SUNY - University at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - United World College, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - University of Cape Town Fund, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - University of Chicago, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - University of the West Indies, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Foundations - A-L, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
    - Foundations - M-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Foundations - The Acorn Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Foundations - Winston Churchill Foundation of the United States, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Foundations - Peter F. Drucker Foundation for Nonprofit Management, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Foundations - Fundación Juan March, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Foundations - Inner-City Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Foundations - George C. Marshall Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Foundations - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Foundations - The Paul Robeson Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Foundations - World War II Memorial Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Historical Societies, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, Rhode Island Historical Society, Saugerties Historical Society.
    - Historical Societies - New York Historical Society, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Housing - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Housing - International House - New York, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 6-7, Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Housing - International House at the University of California, Berkeley, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Housing - International House of Chicago, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Radio-TV - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Celebrity Connection, Children's Television Workshop, Internews, Maine Public Broadcasting, OVATION, Public Radio International, WETA, WNYC Radio.
    - Radio-TV - Center for Communication, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Radio-TV - Thirteen WNET, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Schools - A-H, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Schools - I-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Schools - American Academy in Rome, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Schools - American Farm School, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Schools - New American Schools, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - F-I, 1997-2000; 12; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - F - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic Affairs - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Hispanic Federation, Institute Cervantes (USA), Inc.
    - Hispanic Affairs - Casita Maria, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Contributions, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Horticulture - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Horticulture - Brooklyn Botanical Garden, 1997-2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden, 1997-2000 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - International Relations, 1997-2000; 13; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - International Relations - A-F, 1997-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - International Relations - G-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
    - Africa - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      African Foundation, African Growth and Opportunity Act, African National Congress, Medical Education for South African Blacks, Shared Interest.
    - Africa - Africa America Institute, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Asia - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Asia Foundation, International Asian Art Fair, Overseas Development Council
    - Association for Canadian Studies in the United States, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Council, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - China - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      America-China Society, China Institute in America, Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs, National Committee on United States.
    - China - Culture and Civilization of China, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - CIVICUS - World Alliance for Citizen Participation, 1997-2003 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Colombia - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Moreno, Luis Alberto (Ambassador).
    - Council for the United States and Italy, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Cuba - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Center for a Free Cuba, Brochure from the ARGA Foundation, Helms-Burton's impact on the World Trade Organization and the United States, Permanent Mission of the Republic of Cuba to the United Nations.
    - Cuba - Americans for Humanitarian Trade with Cuba, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
    - Czech Republic - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      American Friends of the Czech Republic.
    - Ecuador - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Fundacion Esquel
    - Finland - Consulate General of Finland (Edgar J. Kaufmann Conference Rooms) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - France - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      La Demeure Historique
    - France - American Society of the French Legion of Honor, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - France - French-American Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - India - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Naresh Chandra, PRASAD Project.
    - International Rescue Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Iran - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Iran - Society for Iranian Studies, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Israel - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Jerusalem Foundation, Jerusalem Fund.
    - Italy - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Ferdinando Salleo
    - Japan - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Japan Center for International Exchange, Japan Foundatipon Center for Global Partnership, Japan Institute of International Affairs, US-Japan Bridging Foundation, Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership.
    - Japan - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Japan - Japan Society, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Jordan - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      The Jordan Society
    - Korea - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Korea Society
    - Kosovo - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Separated Materials
      The Tower Companies
    - Mexico - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Consulado General de Mexico, Embajada de Mexico, Mexican Cultural Institute of New York, Nafta Internship Program, Sociedad International de Valores de Ante Mexico, A.C.
    - Near East Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Panama - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      American Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Panama. Jose Miguel Aieman.
    - Philippines - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      International Institute of Rural Reconstruction, Ramon Magsaysay Awards Foundation
    - Poland - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      Eye Fund for Zuzanna Olszewska, Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture.
    - South Africa - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      Thabo M. Mbeki. South African Institute of International Affairs.
    - South Africa - United States-South Africa Leadership Development Program, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Spain - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Thailand - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      The National Institute of Development Administration, The Thai Support Foundation, Inc.
    - Turkey - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      American Research Institute in Turkey, American Turkish Society, Inc.
    - Venezuela - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Aid - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Aid - The Synergos Institute, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid - Synergos Institute United Nations Dinner, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Policy - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      National Committee on American Foreign Policy
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 10, Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Foreign Policy Association, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - International Advisory Board, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      ACCION International, Caribbean Latin American Action, SBC Warburg Dillon Read
    - Pan American - Americas Society, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Chairman's International Advisory Council, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Contributions, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - David Rockefeller New Initiative Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Pan American - Inter-American Dialogue, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Peace - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Business Executives for National Security, International Peace Academy, Peace Development Fund, Sadat Peace Foundation, United States Institute of Peace.
    - Peace - Bilderberg Meetings, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Nixon Center for Peace and Freedom, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - United Nations - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - Emergency Coalition for U.S. Financial Support of the United Nations, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Executive Council on Diplomacy, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - International Executive Service Corp., 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - United States Government - International Executive Service Corps. - Meetings, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - J-M, 1997-2000; 14; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - K - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Medicine, 1997-2000; 15; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - Medicine - A-C, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 7-8)
    - Medicine - D-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR), 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - American Heart Association, 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - American Italian Cancer Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Drug Strategies, 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Health Commons Institute, 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - New York Blood Center, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Synergy Health Systems, LLC, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - United Cerebral Palsy, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - VZV Research Foundation, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Alcoholism - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Recovery Institute.
    - Hospitals - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
    - Hospitals - Columbia-Greene Community Hospital, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Hospitals - Hospital for Special Surgery, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Rodman C. Rockefeller Renal Cancer Research Fund
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Laurance S. Rockefeller Outpatient Pavilion, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Society of Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Hospitals - United Hospital Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Community Health and Counseling Services, Fountain House.
    - Narcotics - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Albert Greenwood. Hale House. MDI Drug and Alcohol Abuse Group. National Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse. Open Society Institute. Veritas Therapeutic Community Foundation.
    - Narcotics - Phoenix House, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - N-P, 1997-2000; 16; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - O - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Philanthropy, 1997-2000; 17; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Philanthropy - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      American Benefactor, Committee to Encourage Corporate Philanthropy, Copperfield Fund, Chronicle of Philanthropy, Family Wealth and Philanthropy, Linkages in Philanthropy, Maine Grantmakers Association, National Center for Family Philanthropy. Waldemar A. Nielson.
    - Council on Foundations, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Maine Philanthropy Conference, 1998 September 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Politics, 1997-2000; 18; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Politics - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
    - Alexis de Tocqueville Institution, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Reform Project, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Fast Track, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 5-6, Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Mayor's Advisory Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
    - Millard, Charles, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Republican Main Street Partnership, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Population, 1997-2000; 19; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Population - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      International Planned Parenthood Federation, Planned Parenthood of Greater Miami, Inc., Planned Parenthood Hudson Peconic, Planned Parenthood of Westchester and Rockland, Inc., Population Council, Population Institute, Zero Population Group.
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Population Action International, 1997-2000 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Abortion - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL)
  - Race Relations, 1997-2000; 21; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Race Relations - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Associated Black Charities, Black Student Fund, Center for New Black Leadership, Community Renewal Society, Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights under Law, NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, National Ethnic Coalition of Organizations (NECO), National Urban League, New York Urban League, Samaritan Project.
  - Q-R, 1997-2000; 20; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Recreation - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Devon Horse Show Foundation, MDI Community Sailing Center, National Horse Sports Foundation, National Intramural-Recreational Sports Association, Olympic Campaign, Optimal Performance Institute, United States Equestrian Team, Inc.
  - Real Estate, 1997-2000; 22; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Real Estate - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2027
      Birch Brook Subdivision, Boston Properties, Inc., Cushman and Wakefield, Inc., Douglas Hill, Embarcadero Center, Enterprise Foundation, Rockefeller Center Management Corporation, St. Barts, Tishman Speyer Properties, Urstadt Biddle Properties, Inc.
    - Rockefeller Group - A-Z, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2027
    - Rockefeller Group - Rockefeller Center - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills Employees, 1997-2000 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Abeyton Lodge. Beatrix Farrand. Hudson Pines, Kykuit, Playhouse.
  - Religion, 1997-2000; 23; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes